http://indianalaw.to/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search for:
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.IndianaLaw.to.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
IndianaLaw.to only uses Google Analytics and Google Webmaster Tools to monitor website performance.
Occasionally, tools like SemRush.com may be tested, but only for the sole purpose of tracking website performance and finding ways to improve user experience.
Who we share your data with
Your information will not be shared with any third-party websites or companies, unless you specifically request assistance by using a form on this website that clearly states you will be contacted about a specific situation.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact information:
Katherine Zoney can be contacted at katzoney12@yahoo.com. She is the official webmaster of this website.
How we protect your data
IndianaLaw.to does not sell your data to any third-party companies.
What third parties we receive data from?
We receive data from Google Analytics and Google Webmaster Tools. This data is only used to track website performance.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
We are not a law firm. Indiana lawyers have contributed content to this website but IndianaLaw.to is not a law firm. The purpose of this website is to provide free education on Indiana state and federal laws. If you decide to use any of the advice provided on this website, use it at your own risk. We cannot guarantee any type of results from an action that you take which was triggered by anything you read on IndianaLaw.to. IndianaLaw.to does its best to provide accurate information, but due to guest contributors on this website we cannot guarantee everything is 100% accurate.
